[
  {
    "id": "492",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "ML Implementation and Operations",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "SageMaker deployments have two types of usage (select 2)",
      "answers": [
        "Offline usage",
        "Online usage",
        "Big bang",
        "Phased rollout",
        "Parallel adoption"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Offline usage",
        "Online usage"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "493",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "ML Implementation and Operations",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Make inferences on datasets in batch and return results as a set",
      "answers": [
        "Offline usage",
        "Online usage",
        "Big bang",
        "Phased rollout",
        "Parallel adoption"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Offline usage"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "494",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "ML Implementation and Operations",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Entire dataset is needed for inferences; pre-process data before using as an input for another model",
      "answers": [
        "Offline usage",
        "Online usage",
        "Big bang",
        "Phased rollout",
        "Parallel adoption"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Offline usage"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "495",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "ML Implementation and Operations",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Used for predictive models with large historic dataset inputs",
      "answers": [
        "Offline usage",
        "Online usage",
        "Big bang",
        "Phased rollout",
        "Parallel adoption"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Offline usage"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "496",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "ML Implementation and Operations",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Used for feature engineering for a follow-on model",
      "answers": [
        "Offline usage",
        "Online usage",
        "Big bang",
        "Phased rollout",
        "Parallel adoption"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Offline usage"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "497",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "ML Implementation and Operations",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Make inferences on demand as the model is called and return results immediately",
      "answers": [
        "Offline usage",
        "Online usage",
        "Big bang",
        "Phased rollout",
        "Parallel adoption"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Online usage"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "498",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "ML Implementation and Operations",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Need instance response when endpoint is called via an app or service",
      "answers": [
        "Offline usage",
        "Online usage",
        "Big bang",
        "Phased rollout",
        "Parallel adoption"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Online usage"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "499",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "ML Implementation and Operations",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Used for real-time fraud detection",
      "answers": [
        "Offline usage",
        "Online usage",
        "Big bang",
        "Phased rollout",
        "Parallel adoption"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Online usage"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "500",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "ML Implementation and Operations",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Used for autonomous machines",
      "answers": [
        "Offline usage",
        "Online usage",
        "Big bang",
        "Phased rollout",
        "Parallel adoption"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Online usage"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "501",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "ML Implementation and Operations",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 3",
      "question": "The 3 types of ML deployments (Choose 3)",
      "answers": [
        "Offline usage",
        "Online usage",
        "Big bang",
        "Phased rollout",
        "Parallel adoption"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Big bang",
        "Phased rollout",
        "Parallel adoption"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "502",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "ML Implementation and Operations",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Short time, High risk, Cost: function(Risk, Time)",
      "answers": [
        "Offline usage",
        "Online usage",
        "Big bang",
        "Phased rollout",
        "Parallel adoption"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Big bang"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "503",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "ML Implementation and Operations",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Long time, Low risk, Cost: function(Risk, Time)",
      "answers": [
        "Offline usage",
        "Online usage",
        "Big bang",
        "Phased rollout",
        "Parallel adoption"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Phased rollout"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "504",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "ML Implementation and Operations",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Longest time, Low risk, Cost: function(Risk, Time)",
      "answers": [
        "Offline usage",
        "Online usage",
        "Big bang",
        "Phased rollout",
        "Parallel adoption"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Parallel adoption"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "505",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "ML Implementation and Operations",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Sometimes risk is amplified due to concurrency such as data synchronization issues, multiple processes, temporary integrations, etc",
      "answers": [
        "Offline usage",
        "Online usage",
        "Big bang",
        "Phased rollout",
        "Parallel adoption"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Parallel adoption"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "506",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "ML Implementation and Operations",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Natural Language Processing service",
      "answers": [
        "Amazon Comprehend",
        "Amazon Forecast",
        "Amazon Lex",
        "Amazon Personalize",
        "Amazon Polly",
        "Amazon Rekognition",
        "Amazon Textrack",
        "Amazon Transcribe",
        "Amazon Translate"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Amazon Comprehend"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "507",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "ML Implementation and Operations",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Combines time-series data with other variables to deliver highly accurate forecasts (DeepAR)",
      "answers": [
        "Amazon Comprehend",
        "Amazon Forecast",
        "Amazon Lex",
        "Amazon Personalize",
        "Amazon Polly",
        "Amazon Rekognition",
        "Amazon Textrack",
        "Amazon Transcribe",
        "Amazon Translate"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Amazon Forecast"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "508",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "ML Implementation and Operations",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Build conversational interfaces that can understand the intent and context of natural speech",
      "answers": [
        "Amazon Comprehend",
        "Amazon Forecast",
        "Amazon Lex",
        "Amazon Personalize",
        "Amazon Polly",
        "Amazon Rekognition",
        "Amazon Textrack",
        "Amazon Transcribe",
        "Amazon Translate"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Amazon Lex"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "509",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "ML Implementation and Operations",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Create a customer service chatbot to automatically handle routine requests",
      "answers": [
        "Amazon Comprehend",
        "Amazon Forecast",
        "Amazon Lex",
        "Amazon Personalize",
        "Amazon Polly",
        "Amazon Rekognition",
        "Amazon Textrack",
        "Amazon Transcribe",
        "Amazon Translate"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Amazon Lex"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "510",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "ML Implementation and Operations",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Recommendation engine as a service based on demographic and behavioral data",
      "answers": [
        "Amazon Comprehend",
        "Amazon Forecast",
        "Amazon Lex",
        "Amazon Personalize",
        "Amazon Polly",
        "Amazon Rekognition",
        "Amazon Textrack",
        "Amazon Transcribe",
        "Amazon Translate"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Amazon Personalize"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "511",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "ML Implementation and Operations",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Provide potential upsell products at checkout during a web transaction",
      "answers": [
        "Amazon Comprehend",
        "Amazon Forecast",
        "Amazon Lex",
        "Amazon Personalize",
        "Amazon Polly",
        "Amazon Rekognition",
        "Amazon Textrack",
        "Amazon Transcribe",
        "Amazon Translate"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Amazon Personalize"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "512",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "ML Implementation and Operations",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Text-to-Speech service supporting multiple languages, accents and voices",
      "answers": [
        "Amazon Comprehend",
        "Amazon Forecast",
        "Amazon Lex",
        "Amazon Personalize",
        "Amazon Polly",
        "Amazon Rekognition",
        "Amazon Textrack",
        "Amazon Transcribe",
        "Amazon Translate"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Amazon Polly"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "513",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "ML Implementation and Operations",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Provide dynamically generated personalized voice response for inbound callers",
      "answers": [
        "Amazon Comprehend",
        "Amazon Forecast",
        "Amazon Lex",
        "Amazon Personalize",
        "Amazon Polly",
        "Amazon Rekognition",
        "Amazon Textrack",
        "Amazon Transcribe",
        "Amazon Translate"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Amazon Polly"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "514",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "ML Implementation and Operations",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Image and video analysis to parse and recognize objects, people, activities, and facial expressions",
      "answers": [
        "Amazon Comprehend",
        "Amazon Forecast",
        "Amazon Lex",
        "Amazon Personalize",
        "Amazon Polly",
        "Amazon Rekognition",
        "Amazon Textrack",
        "Amazon Transcribe",
        "Amazon Translate"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Amazon Rekognition"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "515",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "ML Implementation and Operations",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Provide an additional form of employee authentication through facial recognition as they scan an access badge",
      "answers": [
        "Amazon Comprehend",
        "Amazon Forecast",
        "Amazon Lex",
        "Amazon Personalize",
        "Amazon Polly",
        "Amazon Rekognition",
        "Amazon Textrack",
        "Amazon Transcribe",
        "Amazon Translate"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Amazon Rekognition"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "516",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "ML Implementation and Operations",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Extract text, content and metadata from scanned documents",
      "answers": [
        "Amazon Comprehend",
        "Amazon Forecast",
        "Amazon Lex",
        "Amazon Personalize",
        "Amazon Polly",
        "Amazon Rekognition",
        "Amazon Textrack",
        "Amazon Transcribe",
        "Amazon Translate"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Amazon Textrack"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "517",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "ML Implementation and Operations",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Automatically digitize and process physical paper forms",
      "answers": [
        "Amazon Comprehend",
        "Amazon Forecast",
        "Amazon Lex",
        "Amazon Personalize",
        "Amazon Polly",
        "Amazon Rekognition",
        "Amazon Textrack",
        "Amazon Transcribe",
        "Amazon Translate"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Amazon Textrack"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "518",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "ML Implementation and Operations",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Speech-to-Text as a service",
      "answers": [
        "Amazon Comprehend",
        "Amazon Forecast",
        "Amazon Lex",
        "Amazon Personalize",
        "Amazon Polly",
        "Amazon Rekognition",
        "Amazon Textrack",
        "Amazon Transcribe",
        "Amazon Translate"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Amazon Transcribe"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "519",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "ML Implementation and Operations",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Automatically create transcripts of recorded presentations",
      "answers": [
        "Amazon Comprehend",
        "Amazon Forecast",
        "Amazon Lex",
        "Amazon Personalize",
        "Amazon Polly",
        "Amazon Rekognition",
        "Amazon Textrack",
        "Amazon Transcribe",
        "Amazon Translate"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Amazon Transcribe"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "520",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "ML Implementation and Operations",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Translate text to and from many different languages",
      "answers": [
        "Amazon Comprehend",
        "Amazon Forecast",
        "Amazon Lex",
        "Amazon Personalize",
        "Amazon Polly",
        "Amazon Rekognition",
        "Amazon Textrack",
        "Amazon Transcribe",
        "Amazon Translate"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Amazon Translate"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "521",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "ML Implementation and Operations",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Dynamically create localized web content for users based on their geography",
      "answers": [
        "Amazon Comprehend",
        "Amazon Forecast",
        "Amazon Lex",
        "Amazon Personalize",
        "Amazon Polly",
        "Amazon Rekognition",
        "Amazon Textrack",
        "Amazon Transcribe",
        "Amazon Translate"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Amazon Translate"]
    }
  }
]